<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<globalConfig xmlns="http://zstack.org/schema/zstack">
    <config>
        <category>kvm</category>
        <name>vm.migrationQuantity</name>
        <description>A value that defines how many vm can be migrated in parallel when putting a KVM host into maintenance mode.</description>
        <defaultValue>2</defaultValue>
        <type>java.lang.Integer</type>
    </config>

    <config>
        <category>kvm</category>
        <name>reservedCpu</name>
        <description>The CPU capacity reserved on all KVM hosts. ZStack KVM agent is a python web server that needs some CPU capacity to run, this value reserve a portion of CPU for the agent as well as other host applications. The value can be overriden by system tag on individual host, cluster and zone level</description>
        <defaultValue>512</defaultValue>
    </config>

    <config>
        <category>kvm</category>
        <name>reservedMemory</name>
        <description>The memory capacity reserved on all KVM hosts. ZStack KVM agent is a python web server that needs some memory capacity to run. this value reserves a portion of memory for the agent as well as other host applications. The value can be overridden by system tag on individual host, cluster and zone level</description>
        <defaultValue>512M</defaultValue>
    </config>

    <config>
        <category>kvm</category>
        <name>dataVolume.maxNum</name>
        <description>Max number of data volumes allowed to attach to single KVM instance</description>
        <type>java.lang.Integer</type>
        <defaultValue>24</defaultValue>
    </config>

    <config>
        <category>kvm</category>
        <name>host.syncLevel</name>
        <description>The number of parallel commands that can be executed on KVM host. A big number may put a host in heavy workload in a busy system. The value must be greater than zero</description>
        <type>java.lang.Integer</type>
        <defaultValue>10</defaultValue>
    </config>

    <config>
        <category>kvm</category>
        <name>host.DNSCheckList</name>
        <description>DNS or IP check list. When adding a KVM host, if all DNS/IP in the list are failed to ping, the adding host will fail.</description>
        <defaultValue>yahoo.com,google.com,baidu.com</defaultValue>
    </config>

    <config>
        <category>kvm</category>
        <name>redhat.liveSnapshotOn</name>
        <description>when set to true, enable the live volume snapshot on RedHat series OS if the libvirt and QEMU versions match the requirement</description>
        <type>java.lang.Boolean</type>
        <defaultValue>false</defaultValue>
    </config>

    <config>
        <category>kvm</category>
        <name>vm.cacheMode</name>
        <description>disk cache optoin:none,writethrough,writeback</description>
        <defaultValue>none</defaultValue>
     </config>

    <config>
        <category>kvm</category>
        <name>vm.consoleMode</name>
        <description>console mode for VM transport protocol. When set to spice, enable the spice protocol connection for VM. Options:[vnc, spice]</description>
        <type>java.lang.String</type>
        <defaultValue>vnc</defaultValue>
    </config>

    <config>
        <category>kvm</category>
        <name>vm.cpuMode</name>
        <description>the cpu mode option, which could be used to enable nested virtualization, options are [none, host-model, host-passthrough]. none: not use nested virtualization; host-model/host-passthrough will enable nested virtualization. When using host-passthrough, VM will see same CPU model in Host /proc/cpuinfo. When using host-model or host-passthrough, VM migration might be failed, due to mismatched CPU model. To use nested virtualization, user need to do some pre-configuration. Firstly, the /sys/module/kvm_intel/parameters/nested should be set as 'Y'; Secondly, the /usr/libexec/qemu-kvm binary should support nested feature as well. </description>
        <type>java.lang.String</type>
        <defaultValue>none</defaultValue>
    </config>

    <config>
        <category>kvm</category>
        <name>vmSyncOnHostPing</name>
        <description>whether to sync VM states from hosts when host ping tasks execute</description>
        <type>java.lang.Boolean</type>
        <defaultValue>true</defaultValue>
    </config>
</globalConfig>
